

# Jeanine NISHIMWE

## Contact

**Address** Kigali-Rwanda

#### **Phone**

+250 780629636

#### **Email**

jnishimwe321@gmail.com

## **Additional Skills**

## Soft Computer skills

- Microsoft Office
- Web Designing
- Graphic design
- System software Development

#### Leadership skills

- Communication
- Volunteering
- Commitment
- Critical thinking
- Decision-making
- Passion
- Energy
- Setting & Accomplishing Goals

#### Teamwork

Team leadership and

#### collaboration

- Good team player
- Time Management

### **Professional Statement**

I am a courageous, self-motivated, committed, responsible and hardworking young lady who believes in success. I have developed a lot, performance-constructor and knowledge in IT services with extensive experience in coordinating the whole construction process, developing system construction budgets and performing site visits. Possessing great leadership skills, a highly professional attitude, and an important ability to remain calm in stressful situations.

## Work Experience

Nov 2016- Present

#### Youth for Christ, Rwanda

Volunteer

- Volunteered with groups and organizations to help make measurable differences for program recipients.
- Help new youth to know more about the Youth for Christ association.
- To entertain the news story about Jesus and New testaments.
- To encourage more youth to be disciples of Jesus Christ.
- · Assisted with special events or programs.
- Used strong interpersonal communication skills to convey information to others.
- Met with other volunteers and program leaders to discuss new service opportunities.
- Provided immediate responses to questions from volunteers.
- Contributed to security during services by monitoring entering guests for signs of weapons or suspicious behaviors.

Jan 2014- Present

#### **Rwandan Red Cross**

Volunteer

- Worked with clients to improve life choices and maximize benefits of programs.
- Collaborated on program operations with volunteers, including offering feedback from participants and improvement recommendations.
- Identified service gaps and located needed resources for individuals, including housing, work placement and other support.
- Educated potential participants on available services and processes to engage in program.
- Oversaw day-to-day activities of residents in Red cross facility.
- Go on field where the accident occurs to help.

Jul 2020 - Oct 2020

## **Bushenge Provincial Hospital**

IT Assistant Intern

- IT assistance in case of IT absence.
- Hardware and software maintenance.
- Network troubleshooting.

Jan 2019 - June 2019

#### Wimana Health Post

Receptionist and Secretary

- · Register patients.
- Help patients to reach the consultation room.
- Make a monthly report and prepare monthly bills.
- · Kept reception area clean and neat to give visitors positive first

#### impression.

- Oversaw inventory activities, including materials monitoring, ordering or requisition and supply stocking or re-stocking.
- Greeted incoming visitors and customers professionally and provided friendly, knowledgeable assistance.
  - Kept records in CRM to maintain customer data.

## Education

July 2019 - Dec 2021

## Davis College Akilah, Kigali -Rwanda

Advanced Diploma

Information System

May 2021 -Nov 2021

## Kigali Film And Television (KFTV), Kigali-Rwanda

Certificate

• Graphic Design And Photography

July 2020 - July 2021

## Moringa School|We Code Rwanda

Professional Development Certificate

• Full Stack Developer|Android Specialization

Jan 2016- Dec 2018

## École Secondaire Saint François Shangi

A Level Certificate For Secondary School (A2)

• Mathematics, Economics And Computer Science

## Languages

English — Fluent in both spoken and written.

French — Not Bad

Kinyarwanda — Fluent in both spoken and written

Swahili — Not Bad

#### References

Pastor Alain IRANKUNDA, EMLR Kibogora

The youth pastor at Kibogora church

And the Leader of Youth for Christ in Western Union of Rwanda.

Tel: 07884045666

Dean of Davis college Akilah campus Paul Swaga

paul@daviscollege.com